A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1971-1972
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: University Committees, 1971-1972
  - Committee- Fulbright Grants 1971-1972 (Box 59)
  - Subcommittee on Enrollment Projections of the Committee on the Future of the University 1971-1972 (Box 60)
  - Committee- Future of the University 1971-1972 (Box 60)
  - Committee- Graduate Awards and Recruiting 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Graphics 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Gwathmey Award 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Housing 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Institutional Analysis 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- International Students 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Jefferson Award 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Special Lectures 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Page-Barbour and Richard 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Library 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Master Plan 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Medical Affairs Policy Board 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Museum 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Names 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- National Medal of Science 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Processions 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Objects of Art 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Placement 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Public Affairs 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Public Occasions 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Radiation Safety 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Records 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - Committee- Rhodes Scholarships 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Registration 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- ROTC Affairs 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Scholarship Funding 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Security and General Safety 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Scholarships, Grants-in-Aid, Loans, and Employments 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Student Activities 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Student Health 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Student Rights and Responsibilities 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Summer Grants 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Summer Session 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Teacher Education 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Traffic Appeals 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Traffic and Parking 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- University Committee on Students 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- University Press 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- University Union 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Virginia Quarterly Review 1971-1972 (Box 62)
  - Committee- Virginia Status of University Students 1971-1972 (Box 62)
- Series III: Special File - Appreciation Letters to Volunteer Students
  - Appreciation letters to volunteer students form President Shannon, 15 July 1971, "A - G" 1971 (Box 63)
  - Appreciation letters to volunteer students form President Shannon, 15 July 1971, "H - P" 1971 (Box 63)
  - Appreciation letters to volunteer students form President Shannon, 15 July 1971, "R - Z" 1971 (Box 63)